yeskey.com 2015-03-17

# 

**  • How can we protect your privacy**  
  
The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy.  
  
**  • Safe purchase at Yeskey.com**  
We want you to feel completely secure when ordering from Yeskey. We use a technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts (or encodes) sensitive information before it is sent over the Internet.  
  
**  • What information will be collected by Yeskey.com?**  
  
As set forth in more detail below, Yeskey ("Yeskey" or "We") collects personal information that you provide when using the Yeskey web site ("Site"). This information includes your first and last name, email address and a password when you create your Yeskey account. You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of certain features, such as "Save for Later," "Address Book" and the other Yeskey services. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.

Yeskey does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the Yeskey Terms of Use. Children under the age of 13 may not use this Site and parents or legal guardians may not agree to the Yeskey Terms of Use on their behalf. If you do not agree to (or cannot comply with) any of the Yeskey Terms of Use, do not use this Site. 

 _Purchase Information_

When you make a purchase from Yeskey, we collect your name and payment method information. We collect this information in order to bill you for your purchase. We also collect information that allows us to ship your order. This includes the name, address, and phone number of the intended recipient(s).  
When you create an account at Yeskey, you can choose to save your billing information in "My Yeskey." You can also save one or more shipping addresses in your Yeskey Address Book. You may change or delete this saved information anytime. Simply go to My Yeskey. Log in with your ID and password, then edit or delete whatever personal information you wish. 

_Services Account Information_

We collect personal information from users who wish to use any of the Yeskey services, including but not limited to, Yeskey's Transaction Platform. In order to use these services you must provide your email address and password or create an account at Yeskey. 

 _Cookies and Other Computer Information_

When you visit Yeskey, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit this Site so we can enhance and customize your online purchase experience.

When you visit Yeskey, you will be assigned a permanent "cookie" (a small text file) to be stored on your computer's hard drive. The purpose of the cookie is to identify you when you visit this Site so we can enhance and customize your online purchase experience.

You can choose to browse on Yeskey without cookies, but without these identifier files you will not be able to complete a purchase or take advantage of certain features of this Site. These features include storing your shopping cart for later use and, in the future, providing a more personalized shopping experience. Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

We also collect certain technical information from your computer each time you request a page during a visit to Yeskey. This information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, your computer's operating system, browser type and the address of a referring web site, if any. We collect this information to enhance the quality of your experience during your visit to this Site and will not sell or rent this information to any third parties.

We also contract with third parties to provide us with data collection and reporting services regarding our customers' activities on this Site and to track and measure performance of our marketing efforts. These third parties may use cookies and may receive anonymous information about your browsing and buying activity on this Site. None of your personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, email address, etc.) will be received by or shared with these third parties.  

**  • How will Yeskey.com use your information?**  
  
Information, such as company name, address, contact person, telephone number, etc., will be posted on Yeskey.com publicly, and accessible to all users. Users should thus exercise caution when deciding to release any information that is identifiable to you. Yeskey.com conducts analysis and research on the above information regarding users' distribution of industry, geographic location, and so on. The purpose of this research is to gain a better understanding of our users, and is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. Yeskey.com maintains the right to share analytic results with its business partners.  
  
**  • What are your and Yeskey.com's individual responsibilities in regards to privacy protection?**  
  
Once receiving your information, we make our best effort to ensure the stability and security on our systems. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure from hacker attacks. Therefore, Yeskey.com cannot make any warranty on the security of the information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. We will disclose your information in good faith when we believe that it is necessary to: 

  1. enforce the provisions of Yeskey.com; 
  2. protect and defend the rights of Yeskey.com, other users, or for public interests; 
  3. contract with third party parties to provide you with better value and service; 
  4. conform to national regulations or legal processes. 

You as a user are strongly recommended to keep your Member ID and password on Yeskey.com safe and secure. To ensure the safety and security of your company and personal information do not divulge your password to others. If you feel that your Member ID or password is for any reason at risk, please contact us immediately.  
  
**  • Disclaimers**  
  
We are not responsible for the privacy protection methods of other websites who are linked to Yeskey.com.  
  
**  • How can you contact us?**  
Should you have any suggestion on our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
